[The biggest main mission yet]
[The Sphinx's Riddle]
[The first quiz battle of "ALL or NOTHING"]
Answer! The head!
- Super Senior!
- Wrong!
[After a deadly chase going back and forth]
Let's go, let's go!
No, no!
We got it.
[Team OB claims prince status]
I'm the prince!
[The pauper's accommodation is right in the prince's front yard]
I can see them back there!
[Bursting with Frustration]
This isn't right! I knew this would happen!
[The ones who have]
The life of a prince is amazing.
[And the ones who do not]
I wanna drink some cola.
People say that when the shock is too big,
you don't remember anything.
[Pauper Ji Sung's unbelievable triple pauper streak]
I don't remember a thing…
[But the sun will rise again tomorrow!]
[WANGGEOZ Sets Sail]
Oh, wow!
[Half Nervous]
It could really be the most difficult.
[Half Excited]
My heart was fluttering.
- We're sleeping there?
- It must be that!
[Today's destination comes into their view]
Wow, that's really huge!
[After the cruise and the temple,]
We even booked out the whole ship and temple.
[this time, on their own island,]
The scale of "ALL or NOTHING" is next level!
[the princes will have their vacation]
Wow, this is cool.
Wow, this is insane.
- This is amazing!
- Wow!
[Everything that lies before them is art]
That place is so beautiful.
- Is that a pool over there?
- This is amazing.
The view is absolutely insane.
It was just so great.
It felt like I stepped right into a movie.
[Welcome drinks just for them]
"ALL or NOTHING"!
[What kind of trip awaits them today?]
[Lee Teuk]
[Shin Dong]
[DAWN]
[Johnny]
[Kim Yo Han]
[Ji Sung]
- Let's go!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Oh!
- Is this the place?
[Cool]
[Sexy]
[The six men here to claim the throne]
- Oh?
- No way, is that it?
[WANGGEOZ gather at the beach and...]
Oh, is it the sand flag game? The sand flag game?
(Motivation max)
Pull out the flag!
[One flag waits for them]
That's the sand flag game, no?
It's that, it's that.
[When you're at the beach, you gotta dig]
- Oh, the sand flag game. - Oh, this?
[a.k.a. the sand flag game]
I've never played this before.
[Something else is getting set up]
Wow, so we're playing the sand flag game here?
This game
isn't the main event
that decides your status.
[A light mini-game since the weather is nice]
Oh, a mini-game.
- Since it's a mini-game, just take it easy.
- Got it.
So, what do we win
by playing this?
It's been a while since we left Korea.
- Gasp!
- So, we thought
[Excited]
this would be the perfect time to give you this.
Oh?
- Could it be ramyun?
- Korean food?!
[With familiar snacks on the line!]
With small snacks on the line…!
Woooaaahhh!
Wow, this is amazing!
[Cup ramyun]
Wow! This is the best!
- I'm going for the Omori one!
- Ji Sung, Omori!
I have to get the Omori.
I seriously have to
get the Omori, no matter what.
Oh, Carbonara...!
[Cup ramyun sparks their competitive spirit]
Alright!
(Stomach growling)
With the ramyun on the line,
[A mini game for the ramyun]
the game we'll be playing is called
"Unwavering Trust".
- "Unwavering Trust"?
- Yes.
"U.T."?
[Unwavering Trust]
[One team member wears a sling harness]
You'll wear a sling harness on your body,
[The other two hold the harness straps]
while the other two hold on tight and support him.
You have to completely trust
your teammates supporting you from behind,
[While hanging on, scoop away the sand]
while quickly scooping away the sand.
You have to get the other team
[Whoever makes their flag fall loses]
to make their flag fall.
Nice! We won!
- Oh, like "Mission: Impossible"?
- That's right.
[A game that requires strength and flexibility]
This is fun, this is fun.
[Paper Dolls]
We definitely have to be the ones hanging on.
First, you need someone light.
DAWN has such an advantage here.
[Easy!]
You're right.
[The team lineup is very important]
So, how are we splitting into teams?
If I can give you a tip
when dividing into teams…
[Team Lineup Tip: 2 power players]
Having 2 power players
[1 tall member]
and 1 tall player
- will be to your best advantage.
- Yeah.
But since I'm a bit short…
[Picking the power players]
Let's go around and share our weights.
[Requesting a weight reveal]
Let's share our weights.
- I'm 61kg!
- 61kg.
I'm 58kg!
[Shocked...]
[W.O.W]
Wow…
I'm around 72 or 73kg.
64kg here.
75kg!
87Kg
The number suddenly shot up.
[The ultimate power player appears]
Hey, you've lost a lot!
- A power player.
- Yeah.
Power player team.
- Midfielders here.
- Yeah, midfielders.
The offense here.
You two play Rock-Paper-Scissors
and pick a power player each.
- Oh, nice!
- Then, how about this?
Let's play Rock-Paper-Scissors
in groups of two, two, two…
[Play Rock-Paper-Scissors between similar player types]
Team Win and Team Lose?
[and split into Team Win vs Team Lose]
That's fair.
- Is it good?
- That's fun, that's fun! Yeah!
[The power players do Rock-Paper-Scissors first]
We'll go first.
- Shoot or lose! Rock-Paper-Scissors!
- Rock-Paper-Scissors!
- Win.
- I'm on Team Win.
- Shin Dong is strong.
- What are you gonna shoot?
- I'm on Team Win!
Hold on. Where do you want to go?
Shin Dong or Johnny?
- Honestly, for me…
- Yeah?
DAWN.. DAWN...!
[A sudden confession from the younger guy]
You gotta work together for this.
He's only looking at DAWN…
[When DAWN said he was 58kg…]
I'm 58kg.
Wow…
[Ji Sung remembered]
And the stone inside
[Opal (58)]
is opal.
[I want him...]
[Opal DAWN...]
But it's because I want to take this home.
For me as well…
Because of this guy…!
[Getting all the votes]
So that team doesn't matter for you?
[The lonely men with zero votes]
It's DAWN!
Oh, DAWN's already been picked!
[Can't resist his lightness]
57… 57 is really…!
Shoot or lose!
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
- Wow, Yo Han.
- Wow, no way!
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
- Win!
- Winner, come this way.
Winner, come this way. Win!
[Team Win: Sports team lineup]
We're a sports team.
[Team Lose: NCT lineup]
We just need to win.
DAWN, where do you wanna go?
- Me?
- Yeah.
DAWN, you said
my energy was good today!
I'm on another level today!
Another level.
[Desperate charm offensive]
Is Ji Sung... on Team Lose?
[Expectations]
Yeah.
Then, Team Win.
[Has no appetite, but is super competitive]
Oh, you gotta win.
[Bitter...]
To prevent you two
from rigging the game,
please do Rock-Paper-Scissors
with your backs turned.
Okay.
Rigging!
[Which team will get Opal Guy?]
Shoot or lose! Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[DAWN wins]
[Happiness / Despair]
Okay, come this way!
- Who is it?
- Is it over?
- Okay, Lee Teuk!
- Yes.
You can go over here.
(Here)
DAWN, come this way.
[When coworkers become teammates.smp]
- Nice, nice.
- It's fine.
[The ultimate power players
and the ultimate featherweight team up]
- Hey, already…
- I got a good feeling!
I'm the prince!!
No… You're not the princes!
- Let's show them our energy too!
- Yeah!
I'm!!
- The prince…
- The paup…
Come on.
[Sorry, sorry]
We have to do it together.
[Unwavering Trust]
[Team Shin Dong / Team Johnny]
[Chapter.6]
[Fear your enemy once,
fear your friend a thousand times]
[Picking the first player to go]
The first person please wear the harness.
Let's get a taste of it first.
[DAWN steps up for Team Shin Dong]
Just try it out, just try it out.
[Ji Sung enters for Team Johnny]
I just need to make sure it doesn't fall, right?
Yeah, just shave off the sand a little bit.
Oh, okay!
First, we need to put this on him.
Wow, this is more legit than I thought.
Let me do this part for you.
Wait, this is… this is big on him?!
[Even the harness is too big for Opal Guy]
Why is this one so big?
[Getting used to the harness belt before the game]
Try it out, Ji Sung. Try it.
You gotta get closer, way closer.
[Careful, careful]
I think you need to prop yourself here.
- Hey, this is perfect.
- Just a bit more.
[Slips]
Oh, he's slipping. Then…
Wow, this is really hard…
[Team Shin Dong practices too]
Ready, go!
[As light as a small dog wearing a harness]
Go forward, little by little.
[Comfortable]
Yeah, that's good, right? This much?
- Yes, totally.
- Okay, then…
Swoosh!
You're so light! So light!
[Perfect trust established]
Hey, he's seriously so light.
My Achilles tendon is short,
so this really hurts!
It hurts?
- Wow, what do we do about this?
- Straighten your back.
Where does it hurt?
[Throbbing pain]
Here…
- His lack of…
- Spread out more
[Ji Sung's stiffness is a big problem]
His lack of flexibility is the problem!
Ji Sung, aren't you flexible?
I'm totally stiff.
[Rising distrust]
Oh…
Let's try using our bodies.
Oh, but this…!
You do have to be flexible here.
[There's unwavering trust in our team]
That aside, we're good at this.
You just have to trust us!
It's not tiring at all!
- Trust us! Trust us!
- Oh, okay, okay.
- Ready to go?
- Yeah, let's do it.
[Round 1: DAWN VS Ji Sung]
Let's decide who goes first with Rock-Paper-Scissors.
Shoot or lose! Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[First move]
- Okay! - Nice.
Going down!
- Whoa! He's going down!
- Nice, very cool!
[Fully trusting his teammates]
Nice, nice.
[Descending slowly]
That's right.
Nice.
[Safe docking]
Okay, and from here…!
That's it. Now, dig!
[Ugh...]
Dig at it once.
Dig however you want to!
Bring it, bring it.
- Well done.
- Okay.
[Springs up]
Oh, okay!
My arms don't reach.
- Go?
- I'll go now.
DAWN really likes this program now.
[Job satisfaction level: Max]
Dda-dda-dda-dda-dda!
Hey, he's good.
Why is he going down so well…?
[Comfortable as if he's resting his knees]
[Swoosh]
Ugh, DAWN, you're so annoying!
- Whoa!
- Hey!
Why are you enjoying it so much?!
We're way too stable!
[Celebratory dance]
Ddan-ddan-ddan-ddan-ddan!
He's going wild, even dancing!
[A forced smile]
I thought you were a robot or AI.
I'll go right away.
If the flag falls first, you lose.
[His competitive spirit fires up]
Okay.
My arms don't reach over there.
[Bold]
Oh.
[What a man!]
Oh!
That's risky!
- Dig just a little bit, a little!
- DAWN, you have to dig a little bit.
[Proud]
Hey Ji Sung, you're good.
This isn't easy.
- Nothing's uncomfortable, right?
- I'm good, Lee Teuk.
Alright, here we go!
Let's go!
DAWN is super hyped right now.
[Teasing, teasing]
That's when you start losing.
[A man who defies gravity]
Yeah, he's so cool! DAWN!
Oh, he's not really digging.
Oh, what?!
[Barren]
- Wow!
- Okay!
- That's right!
- DAWN was born to play this game!
- Ji Sung.
- If we win this time, that flag's gonna fall!
- That's right!
- Endure it just one more time!!!
- Okay!
- Let's go!
- Let's go! Let's go!
Agh… Come here…
[Careful]
[The wind is picking up...!]
[The sea wind suddenly gets strong]
Is it done? Did you do it?
[Nice]
Oof! Hey!
- You have to be gentle now.
- Hey, we're in trouble.
You have to soothe it now.
Ohhhhh!!!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Oh!
[Urgent]
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
- Hurry, hurry, hurry!
- Hurry up, hurry up!
Do it now!!!!!!
[Chaos]
Hurry up!
Hurry, hurry!
This is bad.
Dig to the right side.
- This is no good.
- You have to soothe it, DAWN. Soothe it!
Let's go!
[Determined]
Okay, let's go!
You need to soothe it!
He's suddenly putting on a show!
[Show effect: None whatsoever]
He's suddenly putting on a show.
Easy, easy.
Just a little bit.
Wow, but this…
It won't fall over after that?
[Scratch, scratch, scratch]
Pull?
Should we pull?
- Oh, so annoying.
- Oh, he's doing more.
[Scratch, scratch, scratch]
Oh, so annoying.
He's doing all that he can.
That's right!
- Wow!!
- Oh!!
[After excitedly going back up]
[Plop]
Wow!!
Nice! We won!!
Does that mean we lost...?
The wind was
blowing way too hard.
Nice!
[R1: Team Johnny, WIN]
Ji Sung, great job!
- Good job!
- Oh, but… Oh…
Ji Sung, pick the ramyun!
Choose whatever you want to eat!
- You said you wanted Omori, right?
- Pick what you want!
[Our Ji Sung, choose whatever you want]
I want either Shin Ramyun or Buldak.
[A happy dilemma]
It's finally looking up for Ji Sung!
Oh, thank goodness!
There's almost only one of each.
[Ji Sung's pick!]
There's only one of these.
[The one and only jjajang ramyun]
Oh, good call with Chapagetti.
Oh, you grabbed the jjajang ramyun?
[Jealous]
I really wanted to eat that one.
[Proud]
I really wanted to eat that.
There's only one of those.
- What should we do?
- Let's practice once?
[Next on the offense: Yo Han practices too]
Go down a bit.
[Opal Guy's first time holding the rope]
You just gotta let it go.
No, I'm not using my strength yet.
- You don't have to.
- Oh really?
[Trembling]
Who's playing next? Oh, Yo Han?
[Wobbling]
Uh, oh!
I'm done digging!
It feels like
I'm doing this alone.
This guy…!
What's with this guy?
[Too light to help when it's needed]
Why is he being pulled forward?
Why is he getting pulled down?
Oh, I'm up against Yo Han.
- I feel like Yo Han will be good.
- Is it safe?
I'm good even if I die!
[Round 2: Yo Han VS Lee Teuk]
- "Unwavering Trust", Round 2 will begin! - Let's go!
[Taekwondo Kid is on the move]
When I say to pull him up,
- just stand your ground.
- I'll get started!
Go, go!
Hey, let go a bit, just a little.
Let go more, more.
[Core muscles trained by Taekwondo]
That's right, we're holding on well.
He didn't dig much on this side.
Yeah.
[Relaxed]
Yes, that's it for now.
That's it.
[Sliding]
Hey, Lee Teuk, Lee Teuk!
- Tell us when you're gonna go!
- Oh, got it, got it.
[Still getting ready in the back]
[Charging in]
Oh, Lee Teuk. Tell us when you're gonna go!
[It would've been hilarious if he fell]
You gotta tell us before you go.
I feel rushed.
- Let's go!
- Hold it like this.
Using the sneaky-sneak method!
[Recklessly scooping away the sand]
Up!
Oh, okay.
We're all getting the hang of this!
(Sabotage in action)
Hey, straighten your back, straighten your back!
Should we lift you up?
Yes, I think you can lift me up!
Wow, this is hard.
Wow, you did that well.
[The sand thinned out nicely]
Slowly, slowly.
[Crumbling down]
- Lee Teuk!
- Oh…!
I got this!
Up!
Come on!
Let's hurry up!
We need to do this quickly!
We won this, we won this!
Go down, go all the way down.
[Let's just get through this…!]
Wait, you have
to use the other hand.
Use both hands!
- Wow, he's heavy.
- Wow, but…
- Oh, he's doing well.
- Ohhh…!
Ohhh!!!
- Are you done?
- Wait!
It's moving, it's moving!
[Flag flaps wildly]
Wait, it's moving!
[Wobbling]
Oh, wait!!!
[Will Team Johnny win a second time?]
[Desperate]
Oh, wait!!!
(I'm going)
Agh!!
[R2: Team Johnny wins]
We won!
- What are you doing?!
- No, like, this..! This…!
[Going crazy over how unfair it feels]
No, like, this..! This…!
Hey! You little punk!
[Lee Teuk's pick]
What are Koreans all about?
[A Korean favorite, Kimchi stew ramyun]
Kimchi!
- They're taking all the good stuff!
- That's the tastiest one there!
[Now it's a battle of pride]
The ramyun isn't important here.
We have to win this one.
[The strongest players of each team face off]
Can you loosen this up for me…?
[Embarrassed]
Why is this so small!!
Yo Han was heavy too…
We'll be okay, right…?
- Can you try pulling me up?
- Of course.
- I'll just try it from here.
- Yes, yes.
- Go down?
- Yes.
[Wobbling]
Oh, sorry! Hey, hey!
You can't just pull right away!
- You have to let me go down a bit!
- Sorry, sorry.
Yes, Shin Dong!
[Excessive tension]
[and tremendous distrust]
I was too nervous!
- Go?
- Yes.
- Lower me more!
- You have to let go a bit more.
- Let go a bit more, let go!
Lower me more…
Hold on...!
Shin Dong… Shin Dong…!
Let's just pull him up!
[Doesn't know what happened]
Oh, it's working! It was fine.
- Shin Dong, seriously…
- Are you okay?
I don't think
I can do it twice!
[Shin Dong is too heavy for me…]
I don't think I can do it twice.
[Chaos here too]
Oh, hey! He's too heavy! Oof.
[Just endure this round and you'll win!]
We have to finish it on the first try!
If we endure it, we'll win!
Hey, wait a sec...!
[When's the next round gonna start…?]
Tell us before you go down!
You're heavy right now!
[Intense practice]
Please lower him a little bit.
[Trembling]
[Rapid aging]
Hold on, hold on, hold on!
Pull!!
[Flop]
Pull, pull!
[We're sorry, we cannot pull]
Pull! Pull, guys!
Same there and here.
[Dragging...]
No, DAWN! DAWN!
Why aren't you pulling?
DAWN! What are you doing leaning on me?!
He was leaning on me!
- No… I said I can't…
- Why were you leaning on me…
[The paper doll senior can relate]
Hey, it's so hard, huh?
- I'm going crazy.
- Lee Teuk!
I realized it today!
The Pyramid really
is a wonder of the world!
[Those heavy stones]
It's impossible to build.
[No way humans moved it]
There's no way they moved such huge stones.
[Round 3: Shin Dong VS Johnny]
This is Round 3 of "Unwavering Trust".
- I'll go first!
- Okay.
Their turn could
be over as soon as it begins.
- Then you can start.
- What?
- Trust us!
- Okay.
I'll finish it in one go!
Phew...
- Let's go?
- Ready.
[Tense]
Yes, you can start!
Let it go a little bit.
Let it go a bit more.
Now hold! Just slightly hold on.
[Their lower bodies are leaning way back]
The moment it becomes like this…
[Meanwhile, Shin Dong's sweeping the sand away]
Wait, what is he doing?
Oh, so this is actually possible.
- Is that right?
- Wait! You can only do it once!
[Everyone's startled by the new technique]
How many times are you doing it?
[Just pure torture]
Pull me up!!!
- Pull me up! We got it!
- AGHHHHH!
[Shin Dong's tactic was to save his teammates' stamina]
Hey, come on! That's cheating!
- You have to do it a lot in one turn!
- Is this allowed? Is it?
Where'd that rule come from?
[It's allowed in Ilsan]
From Ilsan. Ilsan.
[Come on, Chicago guy]
Let's see how it's done in Chicago.
[Chicago Guy has an overwhelming reach]
Slowly, slowly!
[Wobbling]
Okay!
Something's off. It looks like
he's propping himself with his fingers.
Up!
[After struggling to lift him up,]
[everyone exits together]
My hands feel like
they're about to fall off.
[It's all about who can hang on longer]
My hand's about to rip apart.
Phew…
[Lol]
Shin Dong, you're not nervous, right?
- Me?
- Yeah.
They're the ones who are nervous.
- Go?
- We were super nervous.
[The faster they do it, the faster the pain ends]
Lower it, just a little bit.
Lower it, lower it.
Hold on!
Pull up! Puuull uppp!
That's it!
- You gotta go, you gotta go.
- Here I go.
Whoaaaa!!
You gotta go.
[Stretch]
Here I go.
[Tremble, tremble]
Hey, watch your eyes!
[A cheeky sand-splitting move]
Oh! So cheeky!
Ha!
[100% serious]
Oh, stop!!
[This isn't fun anymore...]
We can't do this now.
My whole body hurts doing this.
[Having the best time]
Let's go! We gotta hurry.
- Let's go, let's go!
- We gotta hurry.
- We gotta go!
- Lower, lower.
- Gotta go! Just a little more!
- Lower, lower!
Hold it… Hold it…!
Ack…!
- Hold it!
- No!
[Danger]
Oh!
[So fun]
He's kind of leaning forward!
[Careful]
It's gonna fall, it's gonna fall!
Shin Dong, hurry…
- HURRY!!!!
- Oh, wait!
- Pull up! Pull up!
- Hurry!
Pull up!
It's good!
[Plop]
Oh…
[3 wins in a row]
[R3: Team Johnny wins]
Yeah!!!
[Legs give out]
Pick one, pick one!
Your hands feel like
they're gonna fall off, huh?
But I still lost 20kg.
If it were my usual weight,
you would've all died!
Since the first half's over,
we're gonna tweak the rules
a bit to spice things up.
Ooh! A rule change is good.
[Go down at the same time]
You'll simultaneously go down and not come back up.
Oh, okay.
Nice.
- Take turns sweeping while staying in position?
- Yes.
Okay, nice, nice.
[It's all about endurance]
We've got a shot at this.
- Yeah, that'd be pretty okay.
- Yeah.
[Round 4: DAWN VS Lee Teuk]
"Unwavering Trust"! Ready!
Slowly.
[The two come down at the same time]
Slowly, slowly.
- Let's hold it right here.
- Uh, wait, wait.
- First, go down.
- Let's stay here.
This is good.
Press him down from above, DAWN!
I'm good. Up…!
Oh, right, there's no "up"…
[Have to keep swiping sand
while hanging on]
[Basically, a battle of stamina]
Go up about this much… That's it.
- Are you tired?
- A little…
I'm so comfortable.
[Unwavering comfort]
DAWN looks so relaxed.
- Comfort… comfortable?!
- Hang in there.
[This team is dying]
That team's totally about to die.
Are you really tired?
- It's okayyyy…!
- Not even a little tired!
- Mom!
- Come on!
- DAWN, slow down. Let the other team tire out.
- Okay, Shin Dong.
Hrrrgh...!
Haah... Haah...
[Their breathing gets heavier]
[Worried]
I'll lift my back a bit...
[I need to finish this quickly…!]
[Drop]
Ack!
[R4: Team Shin Dong's first win]
We lost, we lost.
- Finally!
- Wow!
[Cheering like they're princes]
Finally, finally!
[Exhausted]
- You okay?
- Fine.
[My hand...]
Finally!
[Choosing ramyun for the first time]
Hey, let's pick one with broth, like Shin Ramyun.
I think I'll go with Buldak Ramen.
[An extremely serious discussion]
Oh, me too.
Since there's only one Buldak left,
let's go with Buldak.
- Yeah, let's grab that one Buldak.
- Right, right.
Wow! Nice!
- Is your hand okay?
- Oh, it feels refreshing.
This must really be difficult.
[An urgent meeting after their first loss]
Should Lee Teuk and I handle this?
Right? That'd be better?
- Oh, there's a new strategy!
- A different strategy!
There's a new strategy!
[Isn't his butt]
Try going down once. Try it.
[too in your face?]
Go down, go down.
- Is this good?
- Yeah, go down.
[A method for Stiff Ji Sung]
[Slip]
But, wait, wait. He's slipping.
[Since he's slipping, then…]
He's slipping, so… Oh, then let's move back.
No, you have to hold him
from the back and grab him.
[Changing into a strange position]
Then… Let's try it.
That's way better.
- I don't think Lee Teuk can hold him.
- I'll try it, I'll try.
How's this?
- Much better.
- Okay.
Everyone, are you feeling tired?
Just a little worn out.
[Round 5: DAWN VS Ji Sung]
I'll go first.
We'll go first.
We'll begin the operation!
[Teasing again]
Alright, go. Keep on going.
[Cheeky flapping]
Please go down, Ji Sung.
Come on down.
- That's it.
- Hold it.
- How's it going, Ji Sung?
- Now, first…!
You good, Ji Sung?
- Yeah, yeah!
- A little higher, a little higher.
- Nice, nice!
- Oh.
- Pull up a little bit.
- Hold on!
[Power teasing]
Let me add some spices.
[This side's energy is fading fast]
Be bold. It's fine.
[being in a terrible position]
The wind's not blowing.
Pull up a bit.
Hurry up while the wind's calm.
Ha…!
But like, everyone's
kind of losing their smiles.
My forearms feel like
they're gonna explode!
- Ha...
- This is the crucial part.
- Ha…!
- Almost there, almost there.
[Their energy is fading along with the sand]
Go easy, go easy!
Oh, I'll quickly go down!
[The flag fell!]
Oh!
- Ugh!
- Oh!
[Whoosh]
Oh, we won.
Did we lose? Did we lose?
- The wind, the wind!
- Agh!!
[Everyone's utterly wiped out]
The wind's really strong.
- Good job, Ji Sung. Good job.
- You all did great too.
Why does it feel
like we're the winners?
Seriously, why does it feel like we won?
[The totally exhausted winners]
I don't think they'll be able to eat ramyun.
I don't think they'll have
the energy to hold up their chopsticks.
[Mid-game check-in]
Okay, right now the total is
4.
1.
Should we do one more round?
[Johnny VS Shin Dong]
Then Johnny and I will do it
[Endurance?]
as a game of endurance.
[Oh, this sounds fun]
I think it'll come out this time around.
Everyone's tired.
Will we be able to hold on…?
[Might die before eating ramyun...]
Right now, there's Shin Ramyun and Yukgaejang.
This is actually
a bigger problem for me.
[Painful groans are heard from everywhere]
Wow, but I'm already so tired.
- Will we be able to hang on?
- DAWN, you're nervous, huh?
- Yeah.
- I'm nervous too.
[Why is this so hard...]
This is seriously tough, right?
[Let's just outlast the other team]
Let's just try to hold on longer than them.
[Round 6: Shin Dong VS Johnny]
Here we go. It's the last round. Ready!
[The two guys slowly lower themselves]
Let's go, let's go, go!
- We have to go down, go down.
- Slowly!
[Almost touching the ground]
I'll go first.
- Okay.
- Sit down a little, sit down a little.
Sit down a little.
We're good now.
Hey, what's this?!
What's happening here?
[Suddenly rolling on the ground...]
- What are you doing?
- Ji Sung…!
- Ji Sung, how can you just suddenly let go?
- What are you doing?
Ji Sung...
He suddenly let go!
[Ji Sung was shaky from the start]
Sit down a little, sit down a little.
[Tried to switch his foot position]
Sit down a little.
[But lost his balance]
We're good now.
Hey, what's this?!
[The game ended anticlimactically]
My heel was off the ground,
so I tried to support it,
but lost my balance.
One more time...
[Yeah, nope]
Just once, just once!
It's okay, it's okay!
From the start…!
You were nervous, huh?
So funny!
Ji Sung!
Did you suddenly
not wanna play anymore?
[Feeling wronged]
I really tried my best!
And with that,
the official round has ended.
Yes.
To eat the ramyun, everyone…
- No way?!
- You need water.
- Are we really playing again for water?
- No way!
- With Kimchi on the line.
- Yes! We need Kimchi.
[Winner takes all]
Only one round.
- One round. Okay!
- One round.
[Game: Hang & Steal the Hat]
It's "Steal the Hat".
- While hanging like this?
- Yes.
Oh, but I'm too tired
to do this now…
- You have to do it.
- I have to do it?
We'll hold him up.
[This team's so confident]
We're totally gonna win.
We have to do it.
We'll win it.
- Let's do this.
- Let's at least bring some Kimchi.
[Team Shin Dong: Yo Han]
It's good, right?
It's good!
[Team Johnny: Lee Teuk]
I feel like they'll be quick.
[Talking trash]
He knows how to use his body,
- but he's kind of bad at things like this.
- I know, right?
Yo Han's good at using his feet,
but not his hands.
- Pretend you didn't hear that.
- Should we do a quick preview?
- A quick preview?
- To see the distance.
[A distance check before the main game]
Alright, here we go. Keep going!
Keep going!
Lee Teuk, come a bit more.
[Burst]
This is fun!
This is fun! This is fun!
[Why are they suddenly laughing?]
This is fun! This is fun! This is fun!
[That was so childish just now]
We're so childish.
- So childish.
- Alright, let's get started.
[A one-round showdown for Kimchi: Yo Han vs Lee Teuk]
One round with Kimchi on the line!
Ready!
[The two slowly inch closer]
Oh, it's happening.
No, I gotta go up!
[Uhehehehehe]
I gotta go up!
I can't go any lower than this!
[Right from the start,]
I gotta move up more!
[Yo Han starts attacking]
I can't go lower!
I really can't go any lower!
Lee Teuk, we're going!
[Johnny loosens the rope just a bit]
Lee Teuk, here we go! Go! Go!
[Here I come…!]
[Almost lost his hat
while trying to steal Yo Han's...!]
[Timing coordination is everything]
But you're way too fast! Too fast!
Right now!!!
[Roar]
A little slower, slower.
[But why is it slowly getting…]
[Giggle, giggle]
Hey, hurry up already!!!!!
Why are these two so happy…
- Why are they so happy?
- Wait, wait!
[What's their deal????]
When are you gonna do it?
[These two are just dying from laughing]
Oh, wait…!
Why are you so happy?
Sorry, but it's only
funny for you two!
It's not fun for us!!
Oh, my stomach!
Wanna give it a try?
It's seriously hilarious!
Seriously hilarious!
["Steal the Hat" recommended for]
If people who don't get along
or are in a fight do this,
they'll end up falling in love.
It's not fun for us!
[Calm down and restart the game]
Let's go! Please blow the whistle!
Ow, my ribs hurt.
Get ready!
[Go]
- Let go! Let go!
- Slowly!
Go!
[Danger]
Go down more! That's it.
- Pfft…!
- Let's go down a little more.
- Hey, your hat!
- You went even lower!
- Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Now's the time, now's the time!
[Seriously, what's wrong with you two?]
Why though?!
They just start laughing
whenever they make eye contact.
It hurts!
[Their laughter somehow
spreads to everyone]
- I'm actually about to cry!
- Try this, just try it!
[Highly recommended]
Can you please just try it once?
- Just try it once…
- It feels strange.
It feels weird!
- This… feels weird!
- Switch players?
- Just try it once, for real!
- Switch players, switch players.
[A precious experience he really wants to share]
DAWN, just try it once.
Switch to DAWN.
Take off your sunglasses!
Look each other in the eyes.
Right?
[The feeling lingers]
Just once…!
It's seriously so hilarious.
It hurts so much here.
Hehehehe...
He's still laughing. Oh, it hurts.
I think it'll come out in my dreams.
[Lee Teuk's face that he saw up close]
His expressions when we got close.
[Player switch due to unstoppable laughing]
Let's try it out.
- Hey, Johnny, try going down.
- I'll give it a try.
Go down.
- Go down, go down.
- I'll hold you.
[They're unable to hold back their laughter]
[See, I told you!]
I told you, right?
I'm telling you, it's true!
[What kind of spell am I under?]
This makes a person look like this!
No, seriously,
you only see from here, like this.
[If you want to be in love,
play "Steal the Hat"…]
I'm telling you, this is hilarious!
Oh, Johnny!
This was actually a really fun game.
[With Kimchi really on the line]
Johnny's really athletic.
[Shin Dong VS Johnny]
Get ready!
[You can't have ramyun without Kimchi]
Come on, Shin Dong's good at grabbing!
[Slips]
Oh, we gotta adjust the position.
We gotta adjust the position.
[After a quick brush]
[He goes right back for it]
[Trying again]
[Shin Dong pushes hard from the start]
[Let's check what happened
from a different angle]
[Behind the fierce duel]
[The supporters wobble]
[This is as far as we go, Captain…]
[We fought with no regrets...]
They're unable to hold on over there.
They're unable to hold on.
[Team Shin Dong wins the Kimchi!]
Kimchi!
- Kimchi!
But why is this game
the most fun so far?
This isn't even
an "ALL or NOTHING" game.
[What even is this…]
I think Cola would be
[Using up all their energy laughing]
more popular in a hot country.
- Definitely.
- Yeah.
[A rare lunch with everyone]
(Quickly recovered his energy)
Wow!
Amazing!
[All prepared for WANGGEOZ,
who worked very hard]
[Pick and eat whatever you'd like]
[Starting with rice / bread / noodles]
[A spread of meat and seafood]
[A perfect meal,
even with sweet and tangy desserts]
[Please enjoy]
(Taking a bite of the risotto first)
Mmm!
[Amazing]
[Eating nonstop]
(Should I bite into it...)
(Let's just eat it all in one bite)
Egypt really knows
how to make a good burger.
[Both cheeks stuffed full]
[It's a burger hotspot?]
I gotta try the burger.
[Jumping on the burger trend]
[The eldest's pick is cream pasta]
[Yo Han follows Lee Teuk's lead
and takes a bite of pasta]
(Taking a bite of the taco)
Wow!
- This is good.
- It's good?
[Agreed]
Yeah, it's good.
[If it's tasty, gotta try it]
Want some? Here, take it.
I highly recommend it.
[Everyone fills up with what they each like]
That's when you eat this quickly.
[A short break before the next schedule]
Oh, I ate so well.
Should we find
a spot to lie down?
- Here?
- Is it here?
- Oh, this is it.
- Wow, this place is so nice.
[Lying down on sunbeds right by the sea]
This is it, this is it!
The water's seriously so clear.
How can it be this clear?
[The refreshing Red Sea
spread out before your eyes]
Something about this clean water
makes me think there are
other edible fish living in it.
Don't most people just call it "fish"?
It's not "edible fish"?
[Anyway]
So, wouldn't there be lots of tropical fish?
But is the water warm?
It's not warm.
Don't tropical fish live in warm water..?
If it's warm… wouldn't they get cooked?
[What is this…?] But they're tropical fish (yeol-dae-eo).
They're not tropical fish because
it has the word "heat (yeol)" in the name.
Then? Are they tropical fish
because there are "10 (yeol)" of them?
[Wow, this conversation is
on a whole different level]
If people overheard us chatting...
They'd think,
"Ugh, these ignorant fools…"
Lee Teuk, please look it up.
[Confident]
Tropical fish are the ones that live in warm water.
(Searching...)
- Oh! Shin Dong!
- Hmm?
They usually live in warm water
around 20 to 30 degrees.
[Fish that live in tropical or subtropical regions]
See? I told you I was right.
Tropical fish… That's why
people who have big aquariums
[Told you I was right]
have to constantly adjust the water temperature.
But our conversation right now...
[Is this even right...?]
Why are we even talking about this...?
[The important thing isn't tropical fish]
Whether a fish's body temperature drops or rises
isn't really important.
[The tropical fish will be fine]
Whether we end up as princes
or paupers is what's important…
Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha Ha!
You and I have been a prince
and a pauper the same amount of times.
That's right.
Sorry to the younger guys,
but if we put in a bit more effort,
we can totally become princes.
[Deciding to play dirty against the younger members]
If we play a little dirty…
Play dirty?
From what I saw,
they don't have much experience,
so they're bad at strategizing.
For a second, this crossed my mind.
"Are we being... too soft?"
[Just how much]
I think we need to try harder to win.
I think we need to
really push ourselves.
[do we have to…]
Hey wait, hold up, lift me up!
[push ourselves…?]
Lee Teuk, what do you think?
Should we team up?
[I'm in!]
Let's team up.
[The Soft Brothers in one team?]
Then should we have another round of Old Boy today?
Let's push hard.
And if the two of us stick together,
people might get suspicious,
so should we recruit someone?
I think DAWN would be perfect.
(Agreed)
I'm thinking DAWN is good.
[Currently all princes]
[DAWN's energy is too strong to ignore]
[Suddenly tired after all the planning]
Alright, I'm gonna nap a little bit.
[And so, the older members chatted away
about tropical fish and playing dirty…]
[And napped to the sound of crashing waves]
(Who are these people…)
[For some reason, it feels like
he's wandering through the underworld]
What are you doing right now?
I'm taking in all of Egypt.
[DAWN, who totally
soaked up Egypt's energy,]
[used that energy to work on music...]
[And found some peace of mind...]
[Clearly a travel YouTuber]
Hey Johnny!
[Found Johnny chilling]
What are you doing on this beautiful island?
Johnny, I'll take your picture.
Can I take a picture of you?
[Sounds good]
Sure.
[Taking pictures of his little bro
with the film camera he brought himself]
Wow!
(Hot guy pose)
That's insane…
Do you take photos often?
I usually don't take them outdoors.
Mostly in studios.
(Prefers studios)
I take lots of photos in the studio.
I'll take photos for you later.
That'd be nice…
[Slightly touched]
Then I'd be thankful.
How much can you pay me?
[I never said it was free.]
[Heh...]
How much can you pay me?
(Thinking)
DAWN, what's your rate?
I charge minimum wage.
[Deal]
Oh, then…!
Then I'll shoot for 2 hours.
(Cheap)
Alright, 22,000 won.
Okay, okay.
[This is the hot guy from Chicago]
The model definitely helps.
[Maximum output for minimum wage]
[The next model is Ji Sung]
Ji Sung, stand over there. Anywhere is fine.
Nice!
[Fixing his hair]
[How do I look?]
[After wrapping up a nice photo shoot…]
Nice!
[He takes a nice stroll with Yo Han in the wind]
Wow.
- Hmm.
- Wow, this wind is really…!
We look like reporters covering a typhoon zone…
[Ready to roll]
We're reporting live on location!
[Kim Yo Han / One-day reporter]
[In awe]
Wow, but this place is just...!
[The endless blue sea stretching beyond the wind]
This place is insane, seriously insane.
This is pretty too, right?
[But]
I was thinking...
I thought,
"It might be okay to be a pauper today…"
[Firm]
I don't think so.
- No, hey!
- If we sleep outside today,
when we wake up tomorrow,
we might be on a different island.
[Paupers flying in the strong wind]
We'll get blown away and end up over there.
I seriously think that might happen!
[Quietly getting pummeled by the wind...]
Wow, but right now, it's really…
(The sand is free of charge)
There's so much sand blowing over.
My throat's burning.
The real problem is...
the wind's only
gonna get stronger at night...
[Correct]
Wow, this place is no joke. What do we do?
[To avoid the wind,
they move to a different spot]
[Curious]
Hey, what happens if you press this doll?
[Wanna hear?]
Just…
[Oh…]
[Shouldn't have asked]
[Proud owner]
[My baby sings well, right?]
Out of all the games so far,
which one was the most fun?
The quizzes for me!
[At Luxor Temple]
"The Sphinx's Riddle"!
Yeah, solving quizzes
was the most fun.
[Thinking back]
Why was I…
so motivated to solve the quizzes?
Why did I try so hard?
Because we saw hope...
[Deep realization!]
Oh! It's because we saw hope!
Even for "Speaking in 9 languages,"
we lost by one language.
- That's right, that's right!
- Because we saw hope…
[Sometimes, hope brings even greater despair]
Ji Sung went crazy.
[Victory is just ahead]
[They racked their brains as hard as they could]
Round 1 goes to Team OB!
[Lost a round with the older members
a step ahead of them]
[Next round flows without a hitch]
- Poppin'!
- Correct!
Correct!
[Hehe! Looks like
we'll really become princes…!!!!!!]
He knows the most about DAWN!
[Not a chance]
I'm the prince!
[Harbored way too much hope]
[Hnng]
- Wow…
- My legs hurt.
He threw water bottles…
[It was like that back then…]
He slid…
[Their break ends with reminiscing]
I don't remember the day I threw the water bottle.
But I think I did.
Let's go.
[WANGGEOZ reunite]
Let's go, let's go.
- Did you enjoy your meal?
- Yes!
When are you having ramyun?
[Saving ramyun for a late-night snack]
At night.
- At night.
- That's right. We'll eat ramyun at night.
Ramyun is actually called "Secret ramyun."
Ramyun tastes best
when you eat it in secret.
We're gonna eat it in secret
when no one's watching or filming.
This is a build-up
for when you eat it all alone, huh?
I don't really like ramyun.
- Wanna play for all the ramyun?
- No.
But from what I heard earlier,
[Getting suspected of something weird]
Shin Dong eats one,
(1 ramyun / 1 ramyun for two)
and these two share one?
[We're gonna share it fairly]
But we have 3 ramyuns.
- Oh!
- They switched one for the Kimchi.
We can each have one.
Did you go for a walk, too?
- Yes!
- Yes.
[Enjoying a rare moment of peace]
You spent a very relaxing time. How was it?
I'm nervous.
[Always suspicious]
Why do you keep giving us these moments?
We don't have time.
Can I make this kind of suggestion?
Let's just be happy today
[Just for today, everyone's a prince?!]
with all 6 of us living the prince's life..!
(Good job, Shin Dong)
We need those kinds of moments.
- Exactly!
- Yeah, yeah!
- We're almost to the end now, right?
- That's right.
The title of this mission is…
"Conversations with the Ancients".
"Conversations with the Ancients"?
Is it a riddle?
Since you're living
in Egypt as princes or paupers,
[Egyptian princes]
as princes, you need to know the history…
as well as understand what kind of
communication took place in ancient times.
[So for this mission,]
We prepared a mission called "Conversations with the Ancients".
This mission is
a status mission!
[A status mission]
Oh…
Wait!
If it's about the ancients, isn't it that?
Like the hieroglyphics we saw.
- Oh!
- Yeah.
That's right.
[Two nights ago at Luxor Temple]
There are murals on the walls too.
[WANGGEOZ]
Yeah, there's something there.
[Discovered ancient hieroglyphics]
This is all text, right?
That's right.
Wow, Shin Dong!
[There's probably a decoding mission]
Something like searching this up and decoding it.
(Reasonable suspicion)
That's totally possible.
[What is it…?]
Do we have to find something?
This mission
doesn't have a long explanation.
The mission starts
as soon as I hand these to you.
First…
- Oh…!
- It's a solo battle.
[Solo battle]
Oh.
[Anxiety creeps in]
Oh, this is gonna be hard.
Ugh! I'm in trouble.
- I'm really bad at things like this.
- It's a solo battle, and…
[Prince status]
This time, the prince status will be given
[Only 2 people]
to only 2 people.
- Oh!
- What?
[Not 3 but 2?]
Is there another category for 1 person?
No, only 2 people will become princes…
- So, 4 paupers?
- 4 people will become paupers.
- We have 10 rooms on this island.
- Yes.
The 2 best rooms
will go to the princes.
[The exact rooms they called dibs on earlier]
Hey, I have to be a prince today.
If I become a prince,
I want room number 4.
Come on! That's not right!
[There are still 8 rooms left...]
Hey, there are rooms left over.
The 8 remaining rooms
will be given to the staff.
- Come on!
- Seriously, just 2 people?
Our equipment has to get charged and stuff.
The staff needs to freshen up as well.
[Then what about us…]
We also need to recharge.
- We need to recharge, too!
- But we have no place to recharge!
- This is quality TV!
- This is so great!
Your "This is so great"
came out so nasally.
This is so great!
[For the mission]
We'll be handing out
notebooks and pens to each of you.
[Notebooks and pens]
Don't open them until I say so.
Oh, don't open them?
Is this the famous
"PD Note" I've heard about?
[Heh]
[Not "PD Note"]
Everyone, take a "PD Note" each.
[Mystery notebooks are handed out]
Oh, I'm curious about this.
I almost opened it out of habit.
[What's written inside…?]
Hey, don't open it yet.
It's got that production vibe.
[Once it's open, it's game on!]
The moment you flip open the first page,
you can start right away.
Start right away?
- Yes, go ahead and open it.
- Open it?
"Obtain the clue next to
a big pool of fresh water."
"The one who finds and understands
the ancient language will become a prince."
"Blessings await those
who bring 'that' to the highest hut."
"The one who uses modern civilization
will beg for eternity."
[Conversations with the Ancients]
[The mission site is the whole island]
[Introducing key spots]
[The building at the very top of the island]
[with rooms for the princes]
[and a dining area]
[is the resort]
[If you follow the path
down from the resort…]
[The swimming pool]
[And 107 parasols dotting the island]
[To become a prince in this place today…?]
I feel like there's a catch…!
[Prince Qualification 1.]
I got it! I just need to find it now.
[Instinct: Trust your gut]
I just feel like there's something over there.
Oh, but I think this is it!
I found it!
- Oh…! Oh!!
- What is it?
What is it? What?
Hold on, what is it?
[Prince Qualification 2.]
There must be something there!
[Speed: Run like crazy]
I need to go over there! This can't wait!
I'll really tell you one.
There's one
all the way at the end.
[Prince Qualification 3. See through the lies]
Is he lying to me because he didn't find it?
- You're lying, huh?
- Then, that means someone lied.
Let's be princes.
There are 2 of us. 2!
Can I just team up with you?
[Is betrayal allowed?]
Can we form teams?
Am I the fool here?
[I'll help you]
I wanna give you the answer.
[Don't trust that]
That's not it.
[There's no one to trust]
I can't trust anyone now.
I'm doomed.
[Sorry, but...]
Sorry.
[The right to be a prince belongs to me]
I really need to…
I really need
to be a prince this time.
[Only two prince spots]
Hurry up!
This is seriously driving me crazy.
- No! This isn't right!
- What? What? What?
Oh, please, please!
[The status mission]
I really wanna be a prince.
[will begin now]
I'm gonna be a prince
"The one who uses
modern civilization…"
[Whoosh]
"will beg for eternity."
[Leaving before reading it all]
- "Blessings await those…"
- Can we go now?
[Dash]
"who bring 'that' to the highest hut."
[Darted off first,
even leaving his assigned camera behind]
[Dash]
[And the 3 who haven't left yet]
A big pool of fresh water.
Fresh water?
[Fresh water...?]
What's "fresh water"?
- We should know what it is before we go.
- Fresh water, fresh water, hold on.
[Sorry, we didn't think you wouldn't know]
I don't know it either. Can I look it up?
You're not gonna tell me?
"Fresh water" and a "pool"?
You know what a pool is.
I really don't know.
I know what a "butt" is.
[Another person who doesn't know what "fresh water" is]
Where's the fresh water?
You gotta find it.
"A big pool of fresh water."
[Let's just go down first]
What's "fresh water"?
[Staff's inner thoughts]
Anyone know what fresh water is?
[Oh no…We didn't think of this scenario]
Fresh water…
Fresh... fresh... fresh.
"A big pool of fresh water."
Fresh water. Is this talking about a pool?
[Is the fresh water a pool?]
Isn't it a pool?
[First to arrive at the pool]
[A big pool of fresh water]
Where's the clue? Where's the clue?
[Immediately thought of the pool]
[Is the clue nearby?]
"A biiig butt of fresh water…"
A big pool!
[Shin Dong heads to the pool too]
[The "pool" is difficult for Chicago Guy]
What's a "pool"?
Just follow the others for now.
[The pool]
Oh, it's exactly that.
But that seems way too easy.
- DAWN!
- Yeah.
What's "fresh water"?
[Fresh water]
"Fresh water" is…
[Like a river or a lake]
It's probably water. Water.
[Water without salt. = Fresh water]
And a "pool"?
[Pool]
A pool is basically filled with water…
[A sunken spot where water collects.]
It's kind of like a pond.
[Much smaller than a swamp.]
[Most likely spot: Swimming pool]
So, actually, that swimming pool is the most likely…!
If I have to solve
these one by one…
"Next to a big pool of fresh water."
Next to a big pool!
Next To!
I came here with the mission!
[Jump]
[First to get the clue]
Let's look at it together!
They can't run
all the way here yet.
- Together, together,
- We're 2 people! 2 people!
[Obtain the clue next to
a big pool of fresh water]
[You get a clue
if you go by the swimming pool]
[Shin Dong gets a clue too]
Okay!
So this is it.
[What's the clue that they got?]
So, what about this?
What am I supposed to do with this?
[After getting the clue,
he searches around the pool]
[DAWN joins them at the pool]
[Passed the clue pickup spot]
It's fresh water!
By the fresh water…!
[A crowd gathers near the pool]
Next to it.
- Are we not understanding this?
- A big pool.
[Chicago Hot Guy's Korean class]
This is the big pool.
Next to it?
Huh? Over there…?
[Even the eldest who came to the beachside]
Is it there?
[changes direction
to the pool, where the crowd is]
Yeah.
That could be it.
If we're going down,
we're going down together
I'm too nervous. I can't do this.
If we're going down,
we're going down together
Huh??
- Huh?
- No way!
He's lying. Such a lie!
You can't pass!
I'm just kidding.
Hey, do you see something there?!
[inaudible]
It must be there. Ugh, I'm doomed.
I'm doomed, totally doomed!
Hey, is there something there???!!!
There's nothing here!
Sorry, Lee Teuk.
There's nothing here.
Is this the fresh water?
I feel like it wouldn't be this easy.
Yeah.
A pool…
(Must make eye contact to get the clue)
[Johnny also gets the clue]
Suddenly…
[Lee Teuk and DAWN still have no clue]
Did I get it right?
Why did you give me this?
[What clue did Johnny get?]
Did I do something good?
[Egyptian hieroglyphics / English alphabet]
(Sold at the market)
[Ancient Egypt hieroglyph decoder]
When I got the decoder,
I immediately thought,
"I just need to find these characters"
Oh!
So,
I have to find something
that looks like this!
[Moving while holding the decoder]
I have to find something that looks like this.
[These hieroglyphics are hidden
somewhere on the island]
[Status of Decoder Holders]
[Obtained]
[Shin Dong / Johnny / Ji Sung]
[Not obtained]
[Lee Teuk / DAWN / Yo Han]
[While everyone's
focused on the fresh water,]
[there's one guy
who chose to go a different path alone]
[Looking around]
[Spotting a suspicious area along the shore]
[Entering like he's under a spell]
[Yo Han, who was
wandering alone, had a thought]
A different… Very…
I'm barking up the wrong tree, huh?
[Type to just charge right in]
[Frustrated]
Ugh, seriously.
How am I supposed
to find the clues?
[Looking around]
[But his gut keeps pointing here]
It feels like something's here.
Wow! This is bad!
I'm in big trouble!
An eagle.
[Found a mysterious eagle drawing]
[Jotting it down before he forgets]
[Found something important
that's clearly suspicious]
[Checking the mission sheet again]
"The highest hut"?
[Next target]
Oh, it's that!
It's that, it's that!
"The highest hut"?
Is this not it?
[Is it not…?]
[Ssp…]
Someone's doing something here.
Why is everyone hiding, though?
It has to be here.
Is it not here?
[Just staff members…]
It's not? It's not? Oh.
[Back to searching for the highest hut]
[The highest hut…]
Where's the highest hut?
[The highest hut is]
Is it not here?
[at the highest place]
Is that the highest hut?
[Since I spotted it,
I need to go over there]
[Climb up the hill]
[And keep climbing
and you'll get there]
The highest hut!
It's here.
[The highest hut: Arrived at HQ]
Did you find it?
Please hand over what you found.
[Clue]
[Handed over the hieroglyph decoder]
[Nope. Go back]
This isn't it.
It's not this?
You have to find it using this.
[Find it using this??]
This isn't the clue,
but there's something else.
There must be another piece of paper…
[Meanwhile, Yo Han spots an eagle]
[Yo Han's biggest strength: Endless stamina]
But where exactly?
Go this way for now?
[Sprinting to the highest hut]
[Cleared the hill in one go
with his insane physical power]
The highest hut!
Did you bring it?
I heard it's for everyone to share?
What is it?
The clue…!
It's not the clue?
["The ancient language" / What Yo Han found]
Based on the clue,
you have to find that item.
[So the eagle wasn't the answer...]
Sigh.
When I read the text,
I honestly didn't understand it.
How do I even find this…?
[Didn't get the crucial clue, the decoder]
I found the clue, but…
The eagle.
This is driving me crazy...!
Let's think about it…
[3 seconds later]
I have no idea.
[Hop! Hop!]
[Ji Sung's collection status: Nothing]
[Pitter-patter]
[Ji Sung just dashes off without thinking]
[To the camera director]
Hello!
[He ran around, but with no luck]
Ugh, this is exhausting.
39?!
What is this?
I don't think it's anything…
[First mysterious paper found]
[What is this...?]
Huh?
Is this right?
[Just a drink menu]
It's the name of things on the menu.
Huh? Why is my phone here?!
I was here earlier during our break.
[Current status]
[Acquired his phone + a menu]
Find the pool! The pool!
[Lee Teuk's Collection Status: Nothing]
[Still searching near the fresh water]
Fresh water...
A butt filled with fresh water.
A pool, not a butt,
but a pool of water.
[An endless freshwater pool loop]
"next to a big pool of fresh water…"
[Like a skit, Johnny appears]
Did you find anything?
- Hey, where'd you get that?
- Uh, Oh!
Where did you get that?
- You didn't get one?
- Yeah.
[Decoder]
Where did you get that?
[Why do only you have it?]
No idea.
What?
- Hey, where'd you pick that up?
- Huh?
- Where did you get it??
- I really don't know...
Honestly, I still don't know
why I got it either.
- Did they give it to you?
- Yeah.
[Feeling left out]
Why? Why didn't I get one?
As I said, I have no clue either.
Why???
- I really don't know.
- Is that the clue?
I have no idea.
[Let's look at it together]
Let me see!
- I honestly wouldn't even if I looked.
- Yeah.
It's just A, B, C, D.
Why didn't I get one?
If you go to
the clue's location, you can find out.
Isn't it the pool? The fresh water?
Everyone went there earlier.
[Why didn't I get one...
What's the reason...]
[Bracing himself and sprinting]
[Heave-ho]
How come you're not
giving me a clue?!
[Waiting for the clue]
Oh, here…!
[Whiny Lee Teuk]
I was here earlier! Why didn't you give it to meee!
What am I supposed to do with this?
[What is it?]
[Yo Han also gets the hieroglyph decoder]
Let's take it slow.
[The first person
to figure out this mission]
A!!
It turns out
[The decoder]
the clue was next to the pool.
And the decoder
had the letter "A".
So, I had to find the pictures,
combine the letters together,
[= A]
and bring it back!
I lost...!
I'm not good at English...
I've only done sports
since I was a kid.
I'm not good at English.
[107 parasols]
[The ancient language
is hidden all over the island]
[Find and piece together
the ancient language]
[Bring "that" to the highest hut]
[Who will decode the ancient language?]
[Yo Han's collection status: A]
[Ran into DAWN while excitedly running around
after getting the language chart]
- DAWN, how many did you see?
- Huh?
DAWN, how many did you see?
You got the clue too, right?
- Huh? You got something?
- Yeah.
[Trying to trade info]
Should we swap clues?
Let's exchange clues.
We can both become princes.
I'll really tell you one.
I even drew it here.
[5 minutes ago, at the hut]
Oh!
[Spotted the eagle!]
Hold up, I need to sketch this out.
It might be hieroglyphics or something.
[Drawing the image
because he didn't get a decoder]
(Honest)
I even drew it here.
[An eagle]
I've got one too.
How many do you have?
Where did you see it?
Just tell me that.
[They both have the same info]
Come on, seriously.
[Revealing the decoder he just got]
You got this too, right?
[What's that...??]
Where'd you find that?
(Over…th…)
For real?
(Urgent)
DAWN! Hurry!
- Let's seriously share this.
- What did you see?
I swear I'll show you.
Let's make a promise!
Promise, promise!
(Nervous)
Oh, wait.
The 2 of us…!
Although it's a solo battle,
[You and me]
2 people can become princes!
I don't think I can.
But I think we saw the same thing.
No, it's not the same thing.
[Clue paper]
Nope, this is my first time seeing this.
[The decoder is the clue]
Oh, this is the language. The language!
[I'm the only one without it]
So, where did you get that language from?
[Secret]
I have no idea...
Seriously, let's share...
[Opening notebook amid distrust]
I'll really show you.
If you show me, I'll show you too.
Oh, it's the same.
The eagle.
- Oh.
- I saw an eagle, too.
Then, where did you get that?
- That's kind of…
- What's the eagle?
[They just give it to you if you go there…]
Come on!
Hey!
- No! This isn't right!
- What? What? What?
- Ji Sung!
- Yes!
Where did you get
that "Ancient Language Chart"?
This is a menu.
No, I mean that Ancient Language Chart.
[Sharing it right away]
Near the pool!
Oh, okay, okay.
[Thanks for the kindness, Ji Sung]
[Dashing straight to the pool]
Is this where we get the decoder?
[All members receive the hieroglyph decoder]
[DAWN also secures an "A"]
A.
[Still "pooling" around, he returns to the pool]
The pool.
The pool?
Shin Dong, how many have you found?
How many have I found?
[Oh, you didn't know]
[Obtained info that there are many]
How many?
[The biiig pool time returns]
"Obtain the clue next to"
[An endless loop]
"a big pool of freshwater."
"The one who finds and understands
the ancient language will become a prince."
[Where is everyone finding them?]
There's nothing here.
Why haven't I found anything?
Wow, I think I'm doomed.
Am I the only one
who can't see anything?
[Ji Sung searches
through parasols like crazy]
I don't think this is it.
Huh?
[Eagle "A" spotted!]
[Oh, so that's how you do it!]
The faster I go,
the sooner I get first place!
I'll find them quickly…!
And be at an advantage!
[Found the lion drawing]
[The second letter, "L"]
Ji Sung, did you see anything?
[Found 2]
Me? Nope, I really didn't see a thing
What did the others find?
[Playing dumb]
No idea... I don't know at all.
Heheh...
Sorry, Lee Teuk…
Today, I really…
I really need
to be a prince this time!
[Sprinting]
Hey, why are you…?
What are you doing?!!!
Where are you going?
Hey, why are you being like that?
(Quietly followed behind him)
[Owl spotted]
[Yo Han spots it too]
[Found the owl!]
[When you decode the owl,
you get an "M"]
[Letters uncovered so far]
["A", "L", "M"]
Hey!
Let's do that!
Let's share!
[Wasp booster ON]
Ji Sung!
I'm gonna be a prince!
Ji Sung, let's share just once!
How many did you find?
"A", "L", "M".
[Dash]
What's "A", "L", "M"?
["A", "L", "M"]
[Honestly shared and then dipped]
But does he not want to check mine?
He just left.
[The hieroglyphic for a lion]
"L"…?
A lion.
I think I know it!
So, it's not just random running.
[Looks like he found an epic shortcut]
[Analyzing the pattern
printed on the mission paper]
Slowly, slowly.
There's no need to rush.
You can do this.
But there's no fish?
Wow, this is really hard.
[Because that's not how it's done...]
[Johnny shows up like a skit again]
No one knows. It's okay. I can do it.
Did you find it?
No, I thought you found it.
I'm still looking.
Like, "Don't leave this area"?
Is there something like that?
[No restricted area]
That's the hut.
So, we just have
to get there in the end.
What am I supposed to interpret?
Oh, so I have to
find the ancient symbols right now.
[Realization while talking]
Oh, what? I'm such an idiot.
[Focusing]
There's definitely something here.
There's gotta be coordinates here…!
Oh!
Where could it be?
Let's think!
After all, a human came up with these questions!
[After a line right out of a shonen manga,
he sprints off]
Right now…
Oh!
I got it!
I just need to find them now!
I need to find this…
I'm sure it's here…
[The area where Yo Han
and DAWN spotted the eagle earlier]
What is this?
Oh?!
Here it is!
It's this! It's this kind of thing!
Yeah, it's finding the letters.
[Lee Teuk Collection Status: A]
"A".
Oh, okay!
I have been really bad at these things
since I was a kid.
Everyone, no matter what you're doing,
take a moment
to look out at the sea...!
[Immersed in the ocean view]
What are we supposed to find?
Wow. This place is amazing!
[Collecting romance instead of hieroglyphics...]
[Johnny can't resist
a heart-shaped decoration]
[Is this right...]
No way it's here.
Come down carefully now.
[Starting to search near the parasol]
Things like this are suspicious.
It's nothing at all.
Then what needs to be here?
Do I have to check inside each one?
Wow!
[Lucky enough to spot
the owl drawing right away!]
When I finally found one,
"Oh! This is what it is!"
It was hidden really deep.
I had to look closely to find it.
So, slowly and thoroughly!
If I'm looking at it,
let me get a proper look!
[Johnny's Collection Status: M]
So I have to check each and every one.
[Charming Chicago hot guy]
[Checking each one meticulously]
Isn't this over the top?
I'm going overboard
doing it like this, right?
[The Search Hamster
is still scurrying about]
[Trait 1: Answers immediately when asked]
[Trait 2: If you suggest sharing,
he only gives his own letters and leaves]
Oh, I'm tired...
[Found a spaceship-shaped hieroglyph]
What is the UFO? UFO.
M, R.
A, L, M, R.
Let's take it step by step.
[DAWN's Collection Status: A]
"The one who finds and understands the ancient language…"
[The ancient language…]
Ji Sung!
Ji Sung!!!
I wish they'd tell us
how many clues there are.
How many did you find?
(Smirk)
4.
- You found 4?
- Yeah.
- For real?
[Pure curiosity]
Where on earth did you find them?
[While DAWN found one,]
Why am I the only one who can't find it?
[Ji Sung found 4]
Did we not check over there?
Did I really not go there?
[Ji Sung runs again]
I don't think I've been here yet!
There's no guarantee
that it's even hanging here.
[Meticulous]
I gotta check the floor carefully too.
Oh, I have been here before!
Dang it.
Ugh, this is exhausting...
Huh?
[Found the cane drawing]
[Found a 'C']
A, L, M, R, C.
[Found 5 in total]
[Current Letter Collection Status]
[1st place: Ji Sung]
[2nd place: Yo Han]
[Tied for 3rd]
[Johnny / DAWN / Lee Teuk]
[6th place: Shin Dong]
Why aren't you moving?
I have to find at least one thing,
[Downcast]
but I couldn't find a single thing...
[Never-ending]
"A big pool of fresh water…"
[Forever trapped in the freshwater pool hell]
This really looks like a clue.
Ji Sung, sorry,
but can I ask you something?
Are the clues written on paper?
- Yeah, they're on paper.
- Oh.
[Shin Dong hasn't seen the ancient language yet]
I haven't found a single one.
So you look at it
and then copy it here?
Rather than writing it down,
you can just remember it.
- How many did you find?
- 5.
You found 5?
There are 5?
Ji Sung, want to share?
I'll solve the puzzle for you.
How's that sound?
[Proposing an investigative alliance]
I haven't found a single clue so far.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Then I'll come find you again later.
- Oh, okay, okay.
(100% on guard)
If you've got five,
I think we can crack the answer.
That's right.
Ji Sung, think it through carefully.
[Coaxing him]
You gotta hurry and become a prince.
Let me find just one more clue,
and I'll come find you!
How did he find those clues?
I'm taking it all for myself!
[Ancient language]
5...?
[Still only found one]
I'm the only one who can't find anything!
[Swish]
[DAWN discovers his second hieroglyphic]
[The letter this image points to is]
Y.
["E/Y" acquired]
[DAWN's Collection Status: A, EY]
Ey…
[E... Y... Why are there 2 of them?]
[DAWN's Collection Status: A, EY]
A.
Ey, A.
[Could it be hidden in the Red Sea?]
[Now everyone's looking through the parasols]
[Folding himself down
to a third of his size to search]
[How Johnny became a "Pocket Man"
while looking for hieroglyphics]
Did I miss them…?
[Only Johnny can't see the hieroglyphics]
From what I can see,
I probably missed a ton of them.
[Losing it]
Alright, let's start from the top.
There must be something there!
DAWN! How many have you found?
- I can't tell you.
- How many have you found?
Let's try finding them together.
[They both need help from each other]
Let me just see how many you found!
Promise me then.
Reveal everything to each other!
Just how many letters you have!
- Huh?
- Just how many you have!
[Doubling up]
I got 4.
[DAWN's Collection Status: A, EY]
[Yo Han's Collection Status: A, M, L]
[Honest]
I found 3.
Really?
You said you had
the "A" from the bird, right?
["A" is the letter they both have]
Oh, the eagle you had too.
[Did the first alliance form in this Hell of Distrust?]
Reveal everything to each other.
[On guard]
Wait, first… Seriously, you…
Seriously, look!
It's real! For real!
I really have it! I found it!
You show me first,
since I showed you earlier.
Together, together.
1, 2, 3!
[The raw reality of trust]
Seriously, ugh!
- You don't have 4!
- No, no! I really do!
[DAWN's Collection Status: A, EY]
You don't have 4!
[Lies are rampant everywhere]
No, it's because I wrote it small here.
[Flap]
Here!
That…
I had an "L"!
"L"…?
[Yo Han shares an "L" with DAWN]
- Don't lie.
- I'm serious.
Let me see.
[Lee Teuk and Johnny pop out like a skit]
I found them too. I found 2!
Huh?
[Whispering]
Let's really show it.
- For real, for real.
- Let's both become princes.
[These punks…leaving me behind]
Ji Sung found 4 right now.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- We gotta find them fast too.
- For real, for real.
Let's really show each other.
Hey, what are you two doing?
I said let's team up!
[Unlike Lee Teuk, who wants an alliance,]
[the younger members are
wary of Lee Teuk's slick moves]
Let's search thoroughly!
Yo Han, look thoroughly!
You can do it!
See? You can do it!
[The same drawing he saw earlier]
What? It's exactly the same.
[The eagle "A" makes another appearance]
Seriously, come on!
[Did he find something?!]
Whose mango juice is this?
I can drink it all?
[The mango juice is suspiciously set up]
Can I really drink it?
It's yummy!
[And so, he drank every drop of that mango juice]
Is there something inside?
There were mango juices
that were set up by the sunbeds.
I thought something was inside if I drank it all,
so I drank it all.
[DAWN found the mango juice too]
There's mango juice here as well.
Why did everyone
leave their mango juices behind?
[Sip]
[Boldly drinking
the juice someone left behind]
[That mango juice
is definitely suspicious]
Why is this mango juice still sitting here?
There's gotta be a clue here.
It's so creamy!
Wow, if I finish this,
is there something in the bottom?
Do I have to take this?
This mango is super creamy!
Mango. Cream.
Mango.
Cream.
Mango cream?
[Found a hieroglyphic of a cane]
[= C]
[Yo Han's Collection Status: A, M, L, C]
C.
[After checking another parasol]
[Yo Han's Collection Status: A, M, L, C, EY]
EY.
(Current Ancient Language symbols: 0)
[Shin Dong stood still
and started rearranging the game]
Ji Sung, I think I roughly understand now.
I think I'm starting
to get something too.
[Ji Sung's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C]
Yeah, so if you share, I'll give you the answer.
I don't know the words.
Let's win over Ji Sung!
There are two princes after all.
If I get hints from
Ji Sung and solve it,
then Ji Sung and I
could become princes.
So, let's ask Ji Sung.
[Mouse Ji Sung is cornered...]
I don't know the words.
If you tell me what they are,
I'll study them with you.
[Opening the notebook like he's hypnotized]
What do you think?
[Ji Sung's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C]
I'm not sure if this is everything.
- I don't know how many there are.
- Right.
[C, A, R, M, L]
Camel.
[Camel…for "camel"]
Camel, camel.
But isn't camel spelled without a "C"?
Camel… It's a "camel".
Camel means "camel"?
You didn't know.
It's a "camel".
[If it's Camel, they need to find a "camel"]
Hurry! Camel!
Camel.
- Camel.
- Huh?
- CAMEL.
Caramel?
Oh, caramel?
[Minibar]
It's not here, right?
- I don't think it would be here.
- Right, where would you get that?
There's a clue near the cameras.
Camera??
Hey, is it the camera??
[The parasols with the letters have cameras]
There were many letters where the cameras were.
[Shin Dong] Ssp…
It's "camel"… Camel.
[Camel]
Or maybe not? Does camel not have an "R"?
"Camel"...?
It has to be
something we can carry.
[Shin Dong takes off running]
[Heavy breathing
but not much speed to show for it]
[The highest hut, HQ]
Answer!
[Answer: Camera]
Camera.
- You're heading in the right direction.
- Yeah, that's right.
[Shin Dong: Failed]
It's a fail.
[Camel]
No matter how I look, there's no camel.
But I don't know English.
I feel like we need to know English...
Do you think
we would give you a hard word?
[Got info that it's an easy word]
It's not a hard word?
[Started studying English in Egypt at age 40]
- Lee Teuk.
- Huh?!
Lee Teuk, where did you find yours?
I got one over there,
and one over here
- I wrote them down in my notebook just now.
- Really?
[Skit Man appears again]
From what I see, this…
[Mouth sealed tight]
Oh, never mind, never mind.
[English Pro: Public enemy #1]
Ugh, seriously! I can't trust these people!
Just tell me one thing!
Huh?
Let's show each other one letter
we found and see if they're right.
[DAWN's Collection Status: A, EY, L]
I wrote mine down. I didn't use my pen.
[Lee Teuk's Collection Status: Z, A]
On the count of three, what I wrote…
Let's just show them at the same time.
[Feeling a bad deal coming]
Seriously.
Seriously. My pen's like this, right?
I wrote mine down earlier, right?
One… Hold on.
[Everyone's public enemy]
Like this, like this.
1, 2, 3!
[Info sharing zone]
Huh?!
Nice!
- Ugh! I really got tricked by you!
- No, it's right!
Then, Lee Teuk, tell me that.
[Johnny's curious too]
Oh, it's something I already have.
Some even overlap with yours.
[DAWN → Lee Teuk]
[Shared "EY"]
[Got "Z"]
[Got "EY"]
[DAWN's Collection Status: A, EY, L, Z]
[The appearance of "Z" that no one found]
I got it!
[Suddenly DAWN starts sprinting]
[Sharp turn]
Okay! Okay!
[Ji Sung's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C]
Wow, but I'm really tired.
What? What?
[DAWN's Collection Status: A, EY, L, Z]
Ugh, I can't find it!
Ji Sung, you found 4?
Did you find more?
Oh, you found them all?!
I... I don't know.
I'm not sure if I found them all,
but I did find more.
- But this doesn't make sense.
- What's going on?
[A little small talk, and off I go!]
[Lee Teuk passes by too]
This is driving me nuts.
I'm almost there! I'm losing it.
[Target spotted]
Ji Sung, how many did you find?
5.
[Ji Sung's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C]
I got 3.
[Lee Teuk's collection status: Z, A, EY]
Let's just show one each.
[Unfair deal detected]
Just one each.
But...
I have 5, and you've got 3.
So just one each!
You get it, right?
You'll see it
as soon as I open it.
[Swift and smooth]
1, 2, 3!
[As if hypnotized by Lee Teuk,
Ji Sung swaps letters]
Oh?
Oh?!
[A cool exit after completing his mission]
Wait, what?
But you said you found 3...
I covered the bottom!
Oh, just show one each. Oh…
[Lee Teuk covered everything but one,
while Ji Sung showed everything]
As I showed him "Z"
and he opened up his notebook,
I peeked over like this.
The younger members
would be chatting with each other, right?
Then I'd sneak a peek from behind.
That's how I got all the letters!
[Ji Sung's collection so far: A, L, M, R, C, Z]
[Ji Sung gets "Z" from Lee Teuk]
Oh, I… Wait.
[Lee Teuk's collection so far: Z, A, EY, L, M]
[Lee Teuk spotted "L" and "M"
in Ji Sung's notebook]
What's this?
[Chaos ensues as "Z" appears]
Wait, what was that?
- [Lee Teuk] What are you doing?
- What?
I haven't found a single clue yet.
- Liar.
- Really.
- Really?
- For real.
But why aren't you making a move?
But for me, I got stuck on fresh water.
- The only fresh water here is that.
- Yeah.
But where do I get the hint from?
Are the hints written on paper?
I haven't found anything either.
Don't lie, Lee Teuk. What is it? Just tell me one.
Lee Teuk!
Please share, Lee Teuk!
[Ji Sung enters HQ]
Are the attempts unlimited?
Did you bring it?
[Answer: Pencil]
We need the item.
Pencil.
Is it related to
the word you found?
[A L M R C Z]
Sort of.
Oh, it's not at all related.
Hold on. Not even a single letter.
Does this even make sense?
Does this word exist in the world?
Have I learned it before?
I found 6!
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
[The One-by-One method]
Then let's show each other just one letter.
- One by one, okay.
- I have…1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
[Shin Dong's Collection Status: A, M, L, R, C]
Oh! I have 6 too.
[Lee Teuk's Collection Status: Z, A, EY, L, M]
Oh, okay then.
[With 20 years of trust]
Lee Teuk, let's just open it.
- Let's just open it together.
- Okay.
- 1, 2, 3!
[Shin Dong's Collection Status: A, M, L, R, C]
[Lee Teuk's Collection Status: Z, A, EY, L, M]
Oh, wait!
Lee Teuk, what's this?
Are you sure you have 6?
Isn't this one?
Lee Teuk, you have a "Z"?
- This one is that.
- What?
- To trick people…!
- Oh, you're trying to trick people.
[The Z was a lie?!]
To trick people…!
"L"… I have that.
[After being totally lost at the beginning of the game]
Yo Han, what did you find?
Ji Sung, did you see something?
[he stumbled into a parasol]
Wait, what's this?
This looks kinda fishy.
[and spotted the resort logo "Z"]
Oh, what? This is in other places too. What the heck.
(Hold up...!)
[Oh...! I got a great idea...!]
[Spotted a target]
[He went to each person, suggesting they show one letter each]
Let's reveal one letter at the same time.
Let's show one letter each.
Let's show each other one letter
we found and see if they're right.
Seriously!
[He gave "Z", and gained "E/Y"]
[He gave a lie, and gained a truth]
There aren't
many words with "Z" in them…
[Wrong info spreads fast...!]
Oh, "Z".
So, there's a "Z".
[Meanwhile, Lee Teuk sneaks a peek]
This is the key.
[Meanwhile,
Ji Sung, who found most of the letters]
A, L, M, R.
[Big prey spotted]
Ji Sung, how many did you find?
Let's just show one each.
[Throwing the strong front-runner into chaos]
Just one each.
You get it, right?
["Z"???]
Oh?
[Hehehe]
[Lee Teuk summons chaos with "Z"]
Wait, what? What's that?
Hey, then, the "Z"…
"Z" could be right.
"Z".
If you take out the "Z"…
Let's say the "Z" is right.
No, I'm just gonna take out the "Z".
[Trapped in the inescapable swamp of "Z"]
But let's say "Z" is right, then…?
He said it's "Z",
but I just don't believe it.
This will haunt me forever.
[Game results that cannot be predicted]
Okay! I got it, I got it!
I can't trust Lee Teuk.
[What'll come of the status mission full of lies?]
I really can't trust Lee Teuk!
This is driving me nuts.
[The clues not yet discovered]
Oh, here it is.
I found it first.
[And the ancient language shrouded in mystery]
Wait, hold on. What's this?
This is driving me crazy.
[Running]
This is no good. I need to check it out myself!
[Begging]
Please!
[Stealing]
Hand me the camera!
[One by one, they get closer]
I found it.
- I figured it out.
- I think this is right!
[And a new alliance forms]
Hey, let's find it together then!
Can I just team up with you?
[The game's been flipped upside down]
Oh! I think you're acting.
- I'll tell you, though.
- No.
[Bring "that" to the highest hut]
Please be it. Please!
- Fresh water.
- Please be it!
Ji Sung, take it slow, will you?
Seriously!
[Who will be the blessed one?]
[Dive into romance]
[In the heart of a scorching summer]
[With the sunset-drenched Red Sea
as the backdrop,]
[a youthful journey full of romance]
Wow!
Apt! Apt!
[As the dreamlike hours pass by]
APT! APT! Uh, uh huh uh huh!
A serious incident has happened.
A ramyun theft!
[Stolen]
How could you touch that?
Seriously!
Hey, was it you?!?!
[Flat-out Denial]
The younger members wouldn't even dream of that!
[Endless distrust]
If you get caught, you won't be forgiven!
It's someone here!
You ate it!
[Their friendship is on the rocks]
It's you, huh?
Why are you ganging up on me?
[Who is the ramyun thief?]
- No, what is this? - What is this?